littleorganics.com.au 2019-03-07

# Little Organics Privacy Policy

#### Security

We use eWay and Paypal as our credit card processor, your credit card details are NEVER seen by or stored on our system.

eWay and Paypal have the highest level of security for credit card transactions and as such your details are very safe. All online purchases and monetary transactions from this site are secured by 128 bit secure sockets layer (SSL), which is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure e-commerce transactions. SSL encrypts all information as you submit your purchase details online.

* * *

#### Privacy

Little Organics respects the confidentiality of our customers. The appropriate measures have been taken to ensure that your personal information kept confidential. We will always make sure that we handle your personal information securely and carefully and will only use your personal information when it is necessary for us to deliver you a service or perform other necessary business functions and activities. Your personal information will never be transferred to a third party for any other reason.

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event, or when purchasing and/or registering Little Organics products. Personal information collected by Little Organics often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular.
